we've both worked with these micro serve
我们都已经使用这些微服务
it it's a bugger to not to put it mildly
不轻描淡写是一个错误
mind my french as a developer you feel
介意我作为开发人员的法语
like you know everything is moving
就像你知道一切都在移动
around you and you just want to
在你周围，你只想
concentrate on the one service that
专心于一项服务
you're trying to develop like how can
您正在尝试如何发展
you have any meet that expectation
你有什么期望
without going completely insane so this
不会完全发疯，所以这
presentation is it's a collection of
演示文稿是它的集合
sorts that we put together over the
我们在
course of the last 12 months or so about
最近12个月左右的疗程
some different ways in which you can
一些不同的方式
lessen the pain okay so will will will
减轻痛苦好吧，这样会
have some pain but we can we can we can
有一些痛苦，但我们可以，我们可以
make it make it feel a little bit better
使它感觉好一点
and we can do put some palliative care
我们可以做一些姑息治疗
at least anyway you both know who we are
至少无论如何你们都知道我们是谁
right this is I'm Dave I'm Spencer I
对，这是我，戴夫，我是斯潘塞，我
live in London I live in Utah I work for
我住在伦敦我住在犹他州
pivotal oh yeah sort of why go figure
关键哦是的为什么要去图
first step is admitting you have a
第一步是承认你有一个
problem yes now that's not a problem
问题是，现在这不是问题
seriously if anybody wants to come and
如果有人要来认真地
join us stick your hand out the kind of
和我们一起伸出你的手
sears afterwards okay so we've got some
之后会灼伤，所以我们有一些
slides right yeah should we have a look
正确滑动，是的，我们应该看看
what's us yeah well says I like this
是什么，我们很好，我喜欢这个
picture this is from what's-his-name's
图片这是从他的名字的
little idea and retriever actually
小想法和猎犬实际上
Schaeffer I think yeah and it's actually
Schaeffer，我想是的，实际上
you know this is a track in the spring
你知道这是春天的足迹
10 calls the cloud native track and
10个呼叫云原生路径和
you've seen cloud native you know
您已经了解了云原生
plastered all over the place anywhere
到处都涂灰泥
does anybody not know what we mean by a
没有人不知道我们的意思是什么
cloud cloud native I'm sure that
我确定
everybody's heard it now okay well done
现在每个人都听说过
thank you yes thank you you don't know
谢谢，是的，谢谢你，你不知道
what the buzz word me we didn't just
我不只是嗡嗡声
invent it I know we picked up a meme I
发明它，我知道我们选了一个模因
think that we've we've run with it quite
认为我们已经在运行它了
a long way especially Andrew so he made
特别是安德鲁，所以他做了很长一段路
this picture and it sort of shows you
这张照片，它显示了你
how all of the pivotal stack so we that
所有的关键堆栈如何
we use every day fitzy
我们每天都健身
with the cloud native philosophy if you
使用云原生哲学
like because it's sort of a movement or
就像是因为它是一种运动或
a state of mind more than actually you
心境比实际更多
know a tool that you can go out and use
知道可以使用的工具
and I think I don't know my I could
我想我不知道我能做到
paraphrase what I think is important
解释我认为重要的
about cloud native it's it's what my
关于云原生这是我的
experience was like when I was working
经验就像我在工作时
in a big distributed system as soon as
在大型分布式系统中
you make the rule right I didn't make
你把规则弄对了我没做
this up but as soon as you have this
这个，但是一旦你有了这个
rule if you write the code you own it
规则，如果您编写自己的代码
you pretty soon learn what cloud native
您很快就会了解云原生
means agree yes yes I do so as soon as
表示同意，是的，我会尽快这样做
you own it I say you maybe you run it or
你拥有它我说你也许你运行它或
maybe you just own it to the extent that
也许您只是拥有它的程度
somebody else runs it be if it goes
有人跑去吧
wrong is he in a call and that's a wake
是他打错电话了吗？
up that's a lesson right and everybody
上课的权利，每个人
learns it quite fast when they're on the
当他们在
end of a telephone at two in the morning
凌晨两点电话结束
or whatever it is which never happened
或从未发生过的任何事情
to me actually because we started
对我来说，实际上是因为我们开始
building stuff as soon as we started
我们一开始就建立东西
building anything that was going to fit
建立任何适合的东西
into a distributed system we started
进入分布式系统，我们开始
following these rules whether we knew it
遵循这些规则，我们是否知道
or not but they didn't I don't think
还是没有，但他们不是我不认为
they'd been codified at that point but
他们那时已经被编纂了，但是
there's this thing called 12 factor
这个东西叫做12因子
anybody heard of 12 factor apps yeah
有人听说过12个因素的应用程序吗
quite a few what's the website 12 pac-12
相当多的网站是12 pac-12
actor net young young yeah so r 0 items
演员net young young yeah so r 0项目
manifest on best practices that they saw
体现他们所看到的最佳实践
as they were building out their systems
当他们建立自己的系统时
yeah and what it comes down to it really
是的，这归根到底是什么
is you know making making it easy to
你知道让它变得容易吗
well there's a couple of things isn't it
好吧，有两件事是不是
it's introspecting but it so that you
这是自省的，但它使您
can tell what's going on in a running
可以告诉跑步中发生了什么
app but it's also from the developer's
应用，但也来自开发者的
point of view it's you know you build
观点是你知道你建立了
the code once and then you can ship it
代码一次，然后就可以发货了
anywhere yeah and it's always the same
在任何地方，都是一样的
table basically yep a way of packaging
表基本上是一种包装方式
and designing your applications such
并设计您的应用程序，例如
that the configuration can come from an
该配置可以来自
external place
外在的地方
the it's a single process it's simple
这是一个单一的过程，很简单
you know it listens you export a port
你知道它在听你出口
that listens on a bunch of different
聆听一堆不同的声音
things that that allow an application to
允许应用程序执行的操作
be moved from environment to environment
从一个环境移到另一个环境
and to be able to reason about it in a
并能够在其中推理
simple way without having to come up
简单的方法而不必上来
with all the rules on your own right
所有规则都由您自己决定
right and actually you know that's a
对，实际上你知道那是一个
discipline but it's a good one because
纪律，但这是一个好习惯，因为
it keeps you honest right keep see it
它使您保持诚实对吧，继续看下去
keeps you on the on the tree path and so
让您一直走在树路上
how do we help well the first thing we
我们如何做好第一件事
do is spring boot right as we've all
做弹簧靴就对了
heard about spring boot makes it really
听说过春季靴子使它真的
easy to write 12 factor apps that's one
易于编写的12个因子应用程序
of its main goals I mean we never phrase
它的主要目标，我的意思是我们从不说
phrased it in that way when we sat down
当我们坐下时以这种方式表达
and wrote it but essentially that's what
并写下来，但本质上就是这样
we're doing so you've got spring and
我们这样做是为了让您拥有春天
spring boots spring clouds sitting at
春季靴子坐在春天的云
the top of this stack making it easy to
该堆栈的顶部使其易于
write the code and then you're deploying
编写代码，然后部署
that into some kind of cloud native
到某种原生云中
runtime what's that that's something
运行时那是什么
where it's easy to take those you know
把你认识的人带到哪里很容易
binary bits and you just sling it in and
二进制位，您只需将其吊起并
it knows what to do with it that's a
它知道该怎么做
platform goodbye so we've got one of
平台再见，所以我们有一个
those is built out of foundry there are
那些是由铸造厂建造的
others that you might you might come
其他你可能会来的人
across we also have one called lattice
横跨我们也有一个叫做格子
which we probably mentioned somewhere in
我们可能在其中某处提到过
this in this presentation I'm not sure
在此演示文稿中，我不确定
with demo it if you went if you didn't
如果没有的话，进行演示
go to matts steins presentation earlier
早些时候去马特斯坦斯演讲
this morning catch it on on the videos
今天早上赶上视频
yeah yeah really good idea assuming it
是的，假设这真的是个好主意
work it is you can't dude great okay and
工作是你不能花花公子好吧，
then there's a bottom layer here as well
那么这里也有底层
which is sort of more infrastructure
这是更多的基础设施
orientated so as a developer I don't
定向，所以我不喜欢开发人员
really don't care about that bottom
真的不在乎那个底部
layer but it's very important right if
层，但是如果
you're going to implement this thing to
你将要实现这个东西
have all three layers so I just thought
三层都有，所以我只是想
I'd bring that up just to just to give
我会提出来只是为了给
us a talking point basically about why
我们基本上是关于为什么的话题
spring boot helps and it's basically
弹簧靴有帮助，基本上
because it helps you to build these
因为它可以帮助您构建这些
binary of things that you can just ship
您可以运送的东西的二进制文件
around and run and everybody knows how
到处跑，每个人都知道如何
to run them because they're very simple
运行它们，因为它们非常简单
and just I like the layers that create
而且我喜欢创建的图层
these nice abstractions another thing we
这些不错的抽象是我们的另一件事
I like about this slide is
我喜欢这张幻灯片是
didn't call it a micro services I like
没有把它称为我喜欢的微服务
the the cloud native term better than
云原生术语比
that partially because micro implies
部分原因是微观暗示
smell something to do with size and just
闻到与大小有关的东西
in speaking with customers they they
与客户交谈时，他们
sometimes get over overworked about that
有时为此过度劳累
that micro and it's it's really about
那个微型，真的是关于
what what context you're in but cloud
您所处的环境是什么，但是云
native describes it a little better and
本机描述得更好，
we try and and take some of the things
我们尝试并采取一些东西
with spring cloud and eliminate some of
与春天的云，并消除一些
the boilerplate that comes with these
这些附带的样板
distributed systems so okay so what are
分布式系统好吧，那是什么
we actually going to talk about the
我们实际上将谈论
developer experience right what's they
开发人员体验是什么
like as a developer in the trenches
就像在战es中的开发商一样
right so that whole side above that was
对，所以那边的整个侧面是
really about yeah I didn't use the word
真的，是的，我没有使用这个词
microservices until now but that's what
微服务直到现在，但这就是事实
it's about right it's it's about an open
是对的，是开放的
flexible architecture which has benefits
具有优势的灵活架构
right in terms of time to market the
就上市时间而言
huge business value there but like I
那里巨大的商业价值，但像我一样
said at the beginning the developer poor
一开始就说开发商差
little developer has he needs to be able
他需要的小开发人员
to work on one thing at a time otherwise
一次只做一件事情
it's pointless right there's no point
这是没有意义的，没有意义
having to build the whole universe every
每次都要建立整个宇宙
time I make a change to a line of code
我更改代码行的时间
and I have I have co-workers former
我有我以前的同事
co-workers here where where we had to do
在这里我们必须做的同事
that we have to rebuild the universe and
我们必须重建宇宙
you know dozens of services to just to
您知道数十种服务
see our that our change worked say yes I
看到我们的改变成功了，是的，我
want tools and techniques are around
想要工具和技术在身​​边
what can we do to help with that a
我们该怎么做才能做到这一点
little bit and of course how can you
一点，当然你怎么能
know the code that would do that we
知道可以做到这一点的代码
wrote and release at last year spring
在去年春天写并发布
one and spring cloud help how can spring
一个和春天的云有助于如何反弹
and how can cloud foundry help us get
云铸造厂如何帮助我们获得
over overcome all lots of the little
克服了所有的小问题
nuances that that can tend to drive you
细微差别可能会驱使您
crazy when you're trying to build these
当您尝试构建这些时会疯狂
applications yeah
是的，是的
okay right so this is this is really the
好吧，所以这真的是
driver for everything if you write a
如果您编写
line of code then I this is the last
代码行，然后我这是最后一个
kind of sociological slide the rest of
某种社会学滑坡
it is all technical and hopefully some
这都是技术性的，希望有些
demos but this is the sort of
演示，但这是一种
organizational structure one the
组织结构之一
Conway's law slide basically if you can
如果可以的话，康威定律基本上是幻灯片
get this mentality in your organization
在您的组织中保持这种心态
if you can get to the point where you if
如果你能做到的话
you build some code if you write some
如果编写一些代码，则可以构建一些代码
code build it then you run it or own it
代码构建它，然后运行它或拥有它
and the rest of the organization
和组织的其他成员
recognizes that and accepts it then
意识到这一点并接受它
you're there basically and you'll know
你基本上在那里，你会知道
when you need to get there you know you
当您需要到达那里时，您知道您
don't necessarily want to do that with
不一定要这样做
for everything straight away but you
为了一切，但是你
probably wanted to be heading there what
可能想去那里
can you do okay so 12 factor principles
能行吗12原则
some of the 12 fracture principles
12条断裂原理中的一些
include things like logs are very
包括日志之类的东西
important log everything collect data
重要日志一切收集数据
even when you don't think you're going
即使您不认为自己要去
to need it because you will eventually
需要它，因为您最终
all right so here's somewhere where
好的，所以在这里
spring boot helps right so actually we
弹簧靴有助于正确，所以实际上我们
didn't use to do this by the fall but by
到秋天没用过
default now I think since 1.2 spring be
现在我认为默认为1.2春季
standard out is the only place where you
标准输出是您唯一的选择
get logs unless you do something like
获取日志，除非您执行类似的操作
you have to elect some other way of
你必须选择其他方式
doing it and standard out is just a
这样做，标准输出只是一个
sensible way to do it because the
明智的做法是因为
operating system knows how to you know
操作系统知道如何知道
help you with that and the platform that
帮助您，以及平台
sits on top of the operating system like
像
the cloud foundry does something special
云代工厂做了一些特别的事情
with standard out right if it's a file
如果是文件，则带有标准输出
in some random location so nobody knows
在某个随机的位置，所以没人知道
about except you that's a snowflake
关于，除了你，那是一片雪花
right nobody's ever going to know where
对，没人会知道在哪里
your logs are if you put them in a file
您的日志是如果您将它们放在文件中
if you put them in stand it out
如果你把它们脱颖而出
everybody knows where to find it that's
每个人都知道在哪里可以找到它
the principle and so spring boob makes
原理，所以弹簧布布使
that really very easy because it's a
真的很容易，因为它是
default its opinionated in that way and
以这种方式违约
it also has this thing called an
它也有一个叫做
actuator which is a set of 41 of better
执行器是一组更好的41个
word non functional features and we're
文字非功能性功能，我们
going to talk a little bit of
要谈一点
those in a minute as a tool but so there
一分钟的工具，但是在那里
are these endpoints like tracing
这些端点是否像跟踪一样
requests ok so if I want to see I found
请求好，所以如果我想看看我发现了
this really very very helpful when I was
这在我当时真的非常非常有帮助
working with a system in production if
如果在生产中使用系统，
something's going wrong first thing you
出事了第一件事你
want to do is find out you know what's
想做的就是找出你知道的是什么
the state of the system you want to get
您要获取的系统状态
a thread dump and you want to get you
一个线程转储，你想让你
know the last hundred requests or
知道最近的一百个请求或
something and see what actually happens
看看实际发生了什么
like what were they trying to do before
就像他们以前想做什么
it went wrong and that was always very
它出了错，那总是非常
valuable and then when you've seen that
有价值，然后当您看到
and you say oh it didn't work why didn't
你说哦，那没用，为什么没用
it work well something's obviously not
它运作良好，显然不是
quite right so what's been configured
非常正确，所以配置了什么
wrong so let's go and look at the
错误的，让我们来看一下
environment endpoint /em for let's go
环境端点/ em让我们开始吧
and look at the mappings and see if
并查看映射，看看是否
actually the endpoint that we're trying
实际上我们正在尝试的端点
to hit is even there so this is the
打到那里，所以这是
reason we provide these these endpoints
我们提供这些端点的原因
so that you can essentially in
这样你就可以
production find out things that are
生产找出东西是
going to be very important if thing if
如果发生以下情况将非常重要
anything goes wrong but at the same time
一切都出错了，但同时
you know but because they are you so
你知道但是因为他们是你所以
useful there they also they also turn
那里有用，他们也转向
out to be useful a development timeline
有用的开发时间表
and I find that and I'm sure if you've
我发现了，我确定你是否
interacted with me on github or a stack
在github或堆栈上与我互动
overflow I've asked you you know what
我问过你你知道吗
does that / end look like what does the
那/结尾看起来像什么
auto config report looked like right
自动配置报告看起来像正确的
what maybe you're missing something in
也许你在想什么
your classpath maybe you know there's
你的课堂路径也许你知道
it's on the classpath but something else
它在类路径上，但还有其他
is missing and so did an auto configure
丢失了，所以自动配置也没有了
like we thought it would and so we can
就像我们认为的那样，所以我们可以
see why something wasn't working it's
看看为什么有些东西不起作用了
generally what I asked yeah yeah we're
通常我问的是的，是的，
doing it about support a lot of the time
很多时候都在做支持
yeah Emily face it it's good for support
是的，艾米丽（Emily）面临着支持
it's good for development time if
如果对开发时间有利，
something goes wrong to find out you
出事了找你
know how you can fix it and it's good
知道如何解决它，这很好
you know when something lands in
你知道什么时候降落
production if the if the the worst
产量如果最差
happens and you have to find out what's
发生了，你必须找出是什么
actually the state of the system the
实际上是系统的状态
data can be there okay on an individual
数据可以存在一个人
service basis so we'll talk about the
服务基础，因此我们将讨论
bigger picture later yeah so
以后再看大图
it's not always going to be a sunny day
并非总是晴天
is it you write this code you get it
是您编写此代码吗？
working locally probably write some
在本地工作可能会写一些
tests ship it right send it send it to
测试将其正确发送给它发送给
the system is it going to work will you
系统会正常工作吗
cross your fingers if it doesn't know
如果不知道，请交叉手指
how are you going to find out so here's
你要如何找到答案，所以这是
a few ideas so logs you can go and look
一些想法，以便您可以查看日志
at your logs if you're in a platform CF
在平台CF中查看日志
logs for instance will get the cloud
例如日志将获得云
foundry logs and actually thought this
铸造日志，实际上认为这
is the thing that I find quite useful
我觉得这很有用
changing the log levels at runtime
在运行时更改日志级别
everybody since like the Year dot has
像Year dot这样的每个人都有
asked us about that you know how do I do
问我们有关您知道我该怎么做
that with my spring spring app and only
与我的春天春天的应用程序，只有
actually pretty recently this time last
其实最近这一次最近
year we demonstrated it right I'm
一年，我们证明了它是正确的
looking you in the spring track so we do
在春天的轨道上寻找你，所以我们
that you know just with a simple
你知道一个简单的
environment variable change while
环境变量同时变化
environment variable not the operating
环境变量不是运行
system but the spring environment you're
系统，但您所处的春季环境
logging levels so that's actually a good
记录级别，这实际上是一个很好的选择
trick to learn and that's actually
学习技巧，这实际上是
through the /n endpoint we post to that
通过/ n端点，我们发布到该端点
logging level dot dots bring framework
测井级点带点框架
security equals debug it's my favorite
安全等于调试，这是我的最爱
because I always want to know why I
因为我一直想知道为什么
can't log in other useful an end points
无法登录其他有用的端点
we chose just talked about another thing
我们选择只是谈论另一件事
that people do is they put in feature
人们所做的就是他们加入功能
switches right so you put in stuff in
切换正确，所以您放入东西
your app that isn't normally active soco
您的应用通常不是活跃的soco
paths that you can activate by again
您可以再次激活的路径
changing the environment variables at
更改环境变量
runtime yeah it's a pretty common thing
是的，这是很常见的事情
to do across especially when you're
特别是当你
introducing you know something new and
向您介绍新知识
you want to say hey some subset of users
你想说嘿，一些用户
do a/b testing on this feature or
为此功能进行a / b测试，或
something like that a pretty common
这样的事情很常见
thing to happen remote debugging is is
发生远程调试的事情是
important I don't know how many times
重要的是我不知道多少次
I've connected had them turn on remote
我已经连接好了，让他们打开遥控器
debugging so I can connect to some
调试，以便我可以连接到一些
server to check it will also see well
服务器检查它也会很好看
maybe talk about
也许谈论
so many tools that that we've been some
这么多的工具，我们已经成为
people on the spring team have been
春季团队的人一直
working on yeah we'll see that later I
是的，我们稍后会看到
think for me remote debugging is a last
对我来说，远程调试是最后一步
resort I only ever do it if I really
如果我真的真的去度假
can't find another way because it's
找不到其他方法，因为
painfully slow usually right yes very
痛苦的缓慢通常是对非常
slowly so but if if there's an app that
慢慢来，但是如果有一个应用程序
just won't behave then you know
只是不会表现那么你知道
sometimes putting a breakpoint in it's
有时在其中放置一个断点
the only way to do it what I hope to be
我希望成为的唯一方式
able to show you maybe maybe maybe it'll
能告诉你也许也许
have to be after this presentation
必须在这个演讲之后
because we've had a Navy issue and I
因为我们遇到了海军问题，而我
can't actually connect my laptop was
实际上无法连接我的笔记本电脑
which will get slides later on and I
稍后会得到幻灯片，我
explained what it's all about was this
解释了这是怎么回事
idea that you could also deploy locally
您也可以在本地部署的想法
so deploying locally is is is the near
所以在本地部署就近了
Varna right that's what you really want
瓦尔纳对，这就是您真正想要的
to do to diagnose a problem the only
做诊断问题的唯一方法
problem with deploying locally is
本地部署的问题是
locally is nino my laptop is not
本地是尼诺我的笔记本电脑不是
necessarily connected to anything else
必然与其他任何事物有关
so the trick is going to be how did you
所以诀窍将是你如何
get a local deployment of a service i'm
得到我在本地部署的服务
working on talking to and interacting
与他人交谈和互动
with a bigger system we know one that
在更大的系统中，我们知道
somebody's deployed in an integration
有人部署在集成中
environment probably and we'll we'll
环境可能，我们会
show you some stuff to do that later on
告诉你一些东西以后再做
so this is just a simple diagram of that
所以这只是一个简单的图
we used last year explaining some of the
我们去年使用了一些解释
key components of spring cloud the
春云的关键组成部分
config server which allows each instance
允许每个实例的配置服务器
to get configuration from centralized
从集中获取配置
location that allows you to version
允许您进行版本控制的位置
configuration and and provide this
配置并提供此
configuration to each instance
每个实例的配置
individually rather than having to
单独而不是必须
package it up with the application the
与应用程序打包在一起
load balancer you see is a client side
您看到的负载均衡器是客户端
load balancer that interacts with the
与负载交互的负载均衡器
service discovery mechanism to get a
服务发现机制来获取
list of available servers that they can
他们可以使用的可用服务器列表
talk to
与...交谈
anything else we want to say about this
关于这个我们还有什么要说的
one and fine with that all right so want
一个很好的，所以想要
to talk a little bit about some of these
谈一些这些
the the common abstractions in spring
春天的常见抽象
cloud that we will use to do some of
云，我们将用来做一些
these these techniques there's a
这些这些技术有一个
discovery client that API is allows
API允许的发现客户端
service to register and then it also
服务注册，然后它也
allows services to say hey I need I need
允许服务说嘿我需要我需要
an instance of service X or Y and it
服务X或Y及其实例
will bring back a host and port
将带回主机和端口
combination a URL basically to a service
基本上将URL组合到服务
that allows you to interact with that
可以让您与之互动
we're list of services and load balancer
我们是服务和负载平衡器的列表
allows is an abstraction over Netflix
allow是Netflix的抽象
ribbon which allows you to plug in and
功能区，可让您插入和
algorithm to decide which of these X
确定这些X中的哪一个的算法
instances should i use it can be round
我应该使用它的实例可以是圆形的
robin it can be random it could be
知更鸟可以是随机的
weighted response time it can be your
加权响应时间可以是您的
own implementation and of course the
自己的实现，当然
annotation to turn this on actually
批注实际上将其打开
that's that's not the right annotation
那不是正确的注释
that's funny okay should be enabled
这很有趣，应该启用
discovery client so so we have spring
发现客户，所以我们有了春天
cloud Netflix which uses Eureka for the
使用Eureka的云Netflix
service discovery and registration and
服务发现和注册以及
of course ribbon is the client side load
功能区当然是客户端的负担
balancer I'm going to go over I actually
平衡器我实际上要过去
have a talk Thursday afternoon I think
我想星期四下午有个演讲
the same time that we'll go over some of
同时我们将讨论一些
these other implementations of service
服务的其他这些实现
discovery and configuration like console
发现和配置，如控制台
from hachey Corp the same guys that do
来自hachey Corp的那些家伙
vagrant if you're familiar with vagrant
如果您熟悉流浪汉
pretty much everybody is patchy
几乎每个人都是零散的
zookeeper is a pretty common
动物园管理员很常见
infrastructure component that people
人们的基础设施组件
from
从
you know from netflix all the way to
从netflix一直知道
they use for coordination and in
他们用于协调和
distributed systems we also have
我们也有分布式系统
implementations of the discovery client
发现客户端的实现
for cloud foundry and lattice that use
用于使用的云铸造和晶格
their api's to for service discovery
他们的api用于服务发现
rather than having some other central
而不是其他一些中央
service running wait yeah so I think the
服务正在运行，是的，所以我认为
next slide is the important one probably
下一张幻灯片可能很重要
because it's actually oh actually we're
因为实际上是哦，实际上我们是
gonna talk about each one first right so
首先要谈每个
before we do that okay so let's just
在我们这样做之前，让我们
distinguish quickly on the previous
快速区分上一个
slide just just just english carefully
小心地滑只是英语
between discovery and load balancing
发现与负载平衡之间
because it's actually the load balancing
因为实际上是负载平衡
that we're going to use in a little bit
我们将要使用一点
to kind of peel open what's going on
剥离一下发生了什么
inside a remote service and try to
内部远程服务，并尝试
manipulate it so that it will help us to
操纵它，以帮助我们
diagnose a problem locally but we're
在本地诊断问题，但我们
doing some local development okay so
做一些本地发展好吧
then we're going to talk about different
那么我们要谈谈不同
kinds of discovery and so the cloud
各种发现等等，云
foundry one is kind of interesting
铸造厂很有趣
because it's read-only right you can
因为它是只读的，所以你可以
discover all the other services but the
发现所有其他服务，但
registration is done for you you don't
注册为您完成，您不需要
actually have a writable registry yeah
实际上有一个可写的注册表
when the learner has some interesting
当学习者有一些有趣的东西时
features when UCF push that's where
UCF推送时的功能
registration happens and then a
注册发生，然后
discovery client would use the the Cloud
发现客户端将使用云
Controller API to find instances that
控制器API查找实例
have already been registered with with
已向进行注册
cloud foundry which then of course can
云铸造厂那当然可以
only tell you a single address for a
只告诉您一个地址
scaled-up app so that's the limitation
扩大规模的应用程序，这就是局限性
of that but it's that's not the only way
但这不是唯一的方法
to do things in Cloud Foundry these days
这些天在Cloud Foundry中做事
yeah there's there's an option to do
是的，有一个选择可以做
direct and then you need posted for
直接，然后您需要发布
trout in a Eureka in that case or a
那种情况下在尤里卡（Eureka）捕鳟鱼
zookeeper or yep which Scott was showing
斯科特所展示的动物园管理员或是
us last night in the yep in the keynote
我们昨晚在主题演讲中是的
in it and lattice when when lattice came
当晶格出现时，它在晶格中
on to the to the scene we I was talking
到我们正在谈论的现场
with with one of the other spring
与另一个弹簧之一
developers last night and how they were
开发人员昨晚的经历
surprised how quickly we came up
惊讶我们走了多快
with the discovery for lattice just
随着晶格的发现而已
because the API was actually so very
因为该API实际上非常非常
simple to use but again it's read only
易于使用，但它也是只读的
when you do a lattice LTC create right
当您进行点阵LTC创建时
that's when registration occurs and we
那就是注册发生的时候，我们
use the one of the api's from one of the
使用其中之一的api
cloud foundry components called Diego
名为Diego的云代工厂组件
some interesting things both about
关于一些有趣的事情
lattice and cloud foundry they add some
格子和云铸造厂，他们增加了一些
profiles by default to your spring
默认情况下为您的弹簧配置文件
applications so that certain auto
应用程序，以便某些自动
configuration can happen for that
为此可以进行配置
particular discovery client and we have
特定的发现客户，我们有
a few connectors that allow you to
一些连接器，使您可以
connect to some basic services database
连接到一些基本服务数据库
messaging yeah I just want to go back to
消息，是的，我只想回到
that profile thing so that think about
该个人资料的事情，以为思考
what that means for beer so so remember
这对啤酒意味着什么，所以请记住
we got this binary tarball thing that we
我们得到了这个二进制的tarball，
want to just move around through
只是想四处走动
environments well this is telling me it
环境很好，这告诉我
something quite interesting right so I
一些非常有趣的事情，所以我
can take the same because I've written
可以一样，因为我写过
it the app in that way I can take the
它以这种方式的应用程序，我可以
same binary distribution I can run the
我可以运行相同的二进制分发
app in Cloud Foundry maybe that's the
Cloud Foundry中的应用程序可能就是
production target but I could have a
生产目标，但我可以有一个
little integration environment using
很少使用集成环境
lattice it's much simpler to set up
设置起来要简单得多
maybe a little bit easier to manage and
也许更容易管理，
interact with the same tarball is going
与同一个tarball进行交互
to run there but it will behave slightly
在那儿跑，但表现会有些微
differently and the slight differences
不同和细微的差异
are all driven by this spring profile
都受这个春天的影响
feature right so you can you can pretty
功能正确，这样您就可以漂亮
safely write the same code at enable
在启用时安全地编写相同的代码
this every client right yo that's why we
每个客户都对，这就是为什么我们
have this abstraction in your spring
在你的春天有这种抽象
cloud application just ship it and run
云应用程序将其交付并运行
it in a number of different environments
它在许多不同的环境中
and it should work in all of them and
它应该适用于所有人
that actually is quite valuable to be
实际上是非常有价值的
able to yet to control and to prove at a
能够控制和证明
development time and integration time
开发时间和整合时间
so we mentioned before you saw Eureka
所以我们在看到尤里卡之前就提到了
running on on a cloud foundry in
在云铸造厂上运行
production I believe Matt showed he has
我相信马特会证明他有
a pretty cool demo of he calls it
他称之为的一个很酷的演示
catalyst it's a lattice application that
催化剂是一种晶格应用
you can download and then with a click
您可以下载，然后单击
of a button you can deploy config server
可以部署配置服务器的按钮
you can deploy Eureka onto lattice if
您可以将Eureka部署到晶格上，如果
you want the more fully featured service
您想要功能更全的服务
discovery on that that particular
在那个特定的发现
platform and we saw the managed version
平台，我们看到了托管版本
of spring cloud services in the demo
演示中的春季云服务
last night we'll see a little more
昨晚我们还会看到更多
tonight yeah so there's that commercial
是的，今晚有商业广告
Eureka instance like the minute is what
像分钟一样的尤里卡实例是什么
it what it is how its implemented using
它是如何使用它实现的
using spring cloud Eureka so that was
使用春天的云尤里卡，所以
that was in the demo last night that's
昨晚在演示中
now a native service and cloud foundry
现在是本机服务和云代工厂
so for a developer you don't have to
因此对于开发人员而言，您不必
write any apps to get Eureka working so
编写任何应用程序以使Eureka正常运行
that's nice but it's sort of interesting
很好，但是有点有趣
is well in a different way as well
也有不同的方式
because like I just said the lattice and
因为就像我刚才说的
cloud foundry service recovery read-only
Cloud Foundry Service Recovery只读
so that's a little bit of a problem in
所以这是一个小问题
some ways right and so actually what I'd
一些正确的方法，所以实际上我会
like and since sometimes is a
喜欢，因为有时是
combination of the tea I don't mind
我不介意喝茶
using the native Cloud Foundry discovery
使用本机Cloud Foundry发现
if that's appropriate may be in
如果合适的话可能在
production that's all I need but a
我只需要生产
development time how about having you
开发时间有你
know a writable registry at the same
同时知道一个可写的注册表
time so that I can you know dynamically
时间，以便我可以动态地知道
register something that I'm building
注册我正在构建的东西
myself and I want to test yeah the
我自己和我想测试
advantage that you gain there is that
你获得的好处是
you could register something outside of
您可以在其他地方注册
lattice or cloud foundry as a an
晶格或云铸造厂
instance of a particular service because
特定服务的实例，因为
you can write to it and then the
您可以写它，然后
services in that cluster know about
该集群中的服务知道
something outside their own environment
他们自己环境之外的东西
and that's I think that's the advantage
那就是我的优势
that marika gives you there so there's
玛丽卡给你在那里，所以
another layer of that as well which is
另一层是
the commercial PCF version of Eureka is
Eureka的商业PCF版本是
very secure because we want enterprises
非常安全，因为我们想要企业
to use it
使用它
but that means that it's not very easy
但这意味着这并不容易
to register an arbitrary random local
注册任意随机本地
locally running application it isn't
本地运行的应用程序不是
going to have the security credentials
将具有安全凭证
to register with a remote Eureka so why
向远程尤里卡注册，为什么
that's interesting is because actually I
有趣的是因为实际上我
can bridge that as a developer if I can
如果我可以的话，可以作为开发人员来桥接
push a Eureka server app bind it to the
推送Eureka服务器应用程序将其绑定到
PCF Eureka that we were using last night
我们昨晚使用的PCF Eureka
and then they become peers so they
然后他们成为同伴，所以他们
actually share a service registry and I
实际共享一个服务注册表，我
can interact with the inner sort of read
可以与内在的阅读互动
only way with the the secure Eureka
安全的尤里卡的唯一途径
through a sidecar essentially one that I
通过一个边车，基本上我
when I've added as a peer that's a
当我添加为同伴时，
little trick that I've been playing
我一直在玩的小把戏
around with and I was hoping to demo
和我在一起，我希望演示
today but I'm not going to be able to
今天，但我将无法
because of the AV problems and this
由于AV问题，这
there's some tooling in sts also which
在sts中也有一些工具
helps you out with that a lot then we
可以帮助您很多，然后我们
you I'll show you some pictures of that
你我给你看一些照片
later there's going to be a diagram that
以后会有一个图
shows how that all fits together so
展示了所有这些如何融合在一起
it'll be it'll be quite an eye-opener
它将大开眼界
when you see it happening ok that's
当你看到它发生的时候，那就是
actually what I was talking about isn't
其实我在说的不是
it more or less so let's say you want to
它或多或少，所以我们说你想
you have this integration system right
您拥有此集成系统的权利
that's the cloud foundry box on the
那是
right-hand side I've deployed all my
在右侧，我已经部署了所有
services up there the whole system is
服务整个系统
running there I don't care how it got
在那儿跑我不在乎它如何
there we'll talk about that later so
在那里我们稍后再谈
there's a service registry part of that
有一个服务注册表部分
platform maybe its native maybe it's an
平台，也许它的本机，也许是
app that I just deployed like I was just
我刚刚部署的应用程序就像
talking about and then there's a remote
谈论，然后有一个遥控器
I'm according a remote client especially
我特别是根据远程客户端
a nap right there's a service which
小睡片刻，有一项服务
wants to contact let's call it red and
想要联系，我们称之为红色，
green right so green service on the
绿色对，所以绿色服务就
right wants to contact the red service
右想联系红色服务
on the left now the red one is the one
现在左边是红色的那个
that I'm working on as a developer so I
我正在从事开发工作，所以我
just cut some code I wrote some unit
只是剪了一些代码，我写了一些单元
tests so everything's fine now I want to
测试，所以我现在想一切都很好
once you integrate it what how can I do
整合后我该怎么办
that without you know slowing everything
没有你就知道放慢一切
down
下
you know sending it all the bites across
你知道发送所有的叮咬
the internet and waiting for them to
上网等待他们
start up and how can I do that so the
启动，我该怎么做，所以
idea with this and because it's a local
这个想法，因为它是一个本地的
change potentially breaking breaking the
变化可能会打破
other people that are trying to use the
其他尝试使用
same integration environment right yeah
相同的集成环境，对
so the key to this is the green thing on
所以关键是绿色的东西
the right hand side the green client
右侧绿色客户
because it's using this service
因为它正在使用这项服务
discovery client side load balancing
发现客户端负载平衡
pattern he actually doesn't really care
他实际上并不在乎的模式
where he sends his requests right he's
他在那里发送请求的权利
just going to ask the service registry
只是问服务注册表
for a red instance and the red instance
对于红色实例和红色实例
might be one of local to him or it might
可能是他的本地人之一，或者可能
be somewhere else it might be in a
在其他地方可能在
different data center or it might be on
不同的数据中心，或者它可能在
my laptop and that's actually the
我的笔记本电脑，实际上是
picture we're drawing here so to make
我们在这里画的图片
this work you need to have two-way
这项工作需要双向
communication probably HTTP or tunneling
通信可能是HTTP或隧道
and other kinds of protocol HTTP is easy
和其他类型的协议HTTP很容易
because tunnels are easy to come by and
因为隧道很容易通过
actually the SDS beaches the spring tool
实际上，SDS使弹簧工具靠拢
suite features that we just built that
我们刚刚构建的套件功能
just came out I was showing you last
刚出来我是最后一次给你看
night in the keynote have sort of one
主题演讲中的夜晚有一种
click service for this so I can right
单击服务为此，我可以
click on a local application and I can
单击本地应用程序，我可以
say build me run this out locally but
说让我在本地用尽
register it remotely and build me a
远程注册并为我建立一个
tunnel back so that the remote services
隧道返回，以便远程服务
can contact me that's really a nice
可以联系我，真的很好
developer experience because now I can
开发人员的经验，因为现在我可以
set real break points i'm running the
设置我正在运行的实际断点
code locally really fast i can set you
本地编码非常快，我可以设置您
know really fast break points and if if
知道真正的快速断点，如果
the right hands if the green service
正确的手，如果绿色服务
sends a request to my red service then
然后向我的红色服务发送请求
i'm going to see the CC at stop and
我要去看CC停下来
that's actually a really interesting and
这实际上非常有趣，
powerful the methodology for developing
强大的开发方法
local applications but key thing is it
本地应用程序，但关键是
relies on the client side load balancing
依靠客户端负载均衡
and that's what we're going to talk
这就是我们要谈的
about next I think so there are a number
关于下一个我想，所以有一些
of different ways that we could achieve
我们可以实现的不同方式
the so in the case that let's come back
所以在我们回来的情况下
here there may be some other red
这里可能还有其他红色
deployed somewhere else
部署在其他地方
right some other red service and how
对其他一些红色服务以及如何
does the remote client when you make the
当您使远程客户端
request no to go back to the one you
要求不回到你的那个
want it to go back to not to the other
希望它回到另一个
one that is on some other machine that
在另一台机器上的那个
you don't have access to right so there
你没有权利，所以在那里
are number of ways we can we can we can
我们可以做到的方式很多
do that we can set a flag in the in the
为此，我们可以在中设置一个标志
remote system that says hey use this
说嘿的远程系统
local route we can determine what looks
本地路线，我们可以确定外观
local right maybe the URL has some
本地权限，可能URL有一些
pattern in it that that we can use to
我们可以用来的模式
switch off of well they another head of
关掉他们的另一头
maybe to hate that arrow right yeah yeah
也许讨厌那个箭头吧，是的，是的
where did this request come from and if
该请求来自哪里以及是否
it came from you know my laptop then we
它来自你知道我的笔记本电脑，然后我们
can route it back to me you might I pay
可以把它寄回给我，我可以付钱
yeah yeah exactly with the header with a
是的，正是带有标题的
request parameter something like that we
请求参数类似我们
can some piece of data that we can use
可以使用一些数据
so that the intelligent router the
这样智能路由器
intelligent load balancer can say I
智能负载均衡器可以说我
actually want to go back to this to this
其实想回到这个
guy zeroth bullet point actually the
家伙零子弹点实际上
default would just be to wait for their
默认只是等待他们
load balancer to come to me right which
负载均衡器来找我吧
happens often enough anyway right i mean
反正经常发生足够正确
if I'm you know developing you know in a
如果我知道你在发展，你就会知道
relatively isolated system and I'm not
相对孤立的系统，我不是
going to tread on too many peoples I'll
踩到太多的人，我会
just do that yeah eventually the
只是这样做，是的，最终
round-robin or random load balancing
循环或随机负载平衡
will hit yours right yeah I guess I
会击中你的，是的，我猜我
could be that's that's the DFAS atif oh
可能就是DFAS atif哦
and Ashley works pretty well nice the
和阿什利工作得很好
time my experience so being able to so
时间我的经验，所以能够
ribbon is this this load balancer that
功能区是这个负载均衡器
clients can use to gain some of these
客户可以用来获取其中的一些
features we've talked about these
我们讨论过的这些功能
different load balancing algorithms one
不同的负载均衡算法之一
of the other abstractions in ribbon is a
功能区中的其他抽象是
server list this says where do i get my
服务器列表这说我从哪里得到我的
list of servers to to get to choose from
要选择的服务器列表
the default one in ribbon is just a
功能区中的默认值只是一个
static list in a property right comma
产权逗号中的静态列表
separated list of URLs which he could
URL的分隔列表，他可以
change the runtime yep
更改运行时
yes with spring cloud you could poke the
是的，春天的云，你可以戳
environment and you could change that
环境，你可以改变它
list if if one of these other server
列出是否这些其他服务器之一
list isn't on the the isn't enabled
列表不在上，未启用
Eureka has a fabulously named I thought
尤里卡有一个神话般的名字，我想
spring was the only one that had have
春天是唯一拥有的
got class names discovery enabled I
启用了类名发现功能
don't even know what I know me and I
我什至不知道我和我
yeah new server list that it would have
是的，它将具有的新服务器列表
been even with if they hadn't previa
即使他们没有previa
console server list zookeeper server
控制台服务器列表Zookeeper服务器
list etc there are also a concept of
列表等也有一个概念
filters what this is allows is too based
过滤这是允许的也是基于
on some piece of information from the
从中获得的一些信息
environment only return a subset of the
环境仅返回
the servers back that were gathered from
从中收集的服务器
the list for example Netflix likes to
例如Netflix喜欢的列表
try and choose a server from the same
尝试从同一服务器中选择一台服务器
zone right they try and narrow the list
他们尝试缩小区域范围，缩小范围
to servers that are actually closer in
到实际上距离更近的服务器
proximity to the client if possible so
尽可能接近客户
so what we're interested in is basically
所以我们感兴趣的基本上是
manipulating that further to send out
进一步操纵发送
traffic to the red service on the right
前往右侧红色服务的交通
a little left right yes yeah correct so
有点左右是是的所以
we've introduced with ribbon by default
默认情况下，我们引入了功能区
it uses properties to change these
它使用属性来更改这些
implementations has some limitations in
实现在以下方面有一些限制
that it it you know creates those
你知道的创造那些
instances for you but we need a little
实例给您，但我们需要一点
more control so Dave actually came up
更多的控制权，所以戴夫实际上出现了
with this method of using annotations to
使用注释的方法
allow us to contain the ribbon
让我们容纳丝带
configuration / ribbon client and when I
配置/功能区客户端，当我
say client i mean the ribbon client for
说客户，我的意思是功能区客户
the red service for example the question
红色服务例如问题
over here
在这里
okay to questions this is a two
好的，这是两个
questions about what we see in the field
关于我们在现场看到的问题
basically right you asking about what
基本上你问什么
we've seen kind of people using the way
我们已经看到一些人使用这种方式
we people see we see people using these
我们看到的人们看到人们使用这些
things yeah so have we seen people using
是的，所以我们看到人们使用了
you reek appears we have absolutely i
你的脸看来我们绝对有
mean that's actually the way it's built
意味着这实际上就是它的构建方式
to be used and the other question was
被使用，另一个问题是
gotta fit on a front end load balance
必须适合前端负载平衡
right now do people use yeah so for
现在人们会用耶
example Cloud Foundry has its own load
示例Cloud Foundry有自己的负载
balance or in front right and you know
平衡或右前方，你知道
for external requests that come in it
对于其中的外部请求
goes through that load balancer and then
经过那个负载均衡器，然后
depending on how you've compared to
取决于您与
excuse me configured Cloud Foundry you
请问我配置了Cloud Foundry吗
can either go back through that router
可以通过该路由器返回
to get to other services or go directly
去其他服务或直接去
to the individual services proxies in
到各个服务代理中
front and load balances aren't replaced
前端和负载平衡不会被替换
by the client side ones is just
在客户端的只是
client-side ones give you some you know
客户端的给你一些你知道的
algorithms to play with you can actually
实际上可以玩的算法
control of the process in a bit more of
控制过程更多
a rational way right it's not you're not
合理的方法不是你不是
just one size fits all you can actually
仅一种尺寸就可以满足您的实际需求
adjust it according to your needs /
根据您的需要进行调整/
client that's what that's why would
客户就是这就是为什么
Spencer was just talking about so a
斯宾塞只是在谈论一个
client in this case is actually I think
在这种情况下，客户实际上是我认为
if it is kind of upside down right is
如果这是一种颠倒的权利
it's really which service do I want to
我真的想提供哪项服务
talk to right so if I want to talk to
说对了，所以如果我想和
the red service I need a ribbon client
红色服务我需要功能区客户端
called red yep exactly one of the places
被称为是红色的地方
that we have used this customization
我们已经使用了这种定制
spring boot has some fantastic
春季靴子有些神奇
integration test capabilities right it
集成测试功能吧
spins up your actual spring boot service
启动实际的Spring Boot服务
and you can write tests that you know do
您可以编写自己知道的测试
real HTTP communication with your real
与您的真实HTTP通信
service it's it's it's really useful we
服务，这是非常有用的我们
use it in spring cloud to test various
在Spring Cloud中使用它来测试各种
features and one of the things we we do
功能和我们要做的事情之一
if you can you can see here you can see
如果可以的话，可以在这里看到
some of the things that I was talking
我在说一些事情
about so here is a the ribbon client
大约这是一个功能区客户端
annotation I want it to be for
我希望它用于
contacting the service called local app
联系称为本地应用程序的服务
and the configuration for that client is
该客户端的配置为
coming from this class
来自这个阶层
and so down here you can see it's just a
所以在这里，您可以看到它只是一个
basic spring java configuration class
基本的Spring Java配置类
this this value here comes from the
这个值来自这里
spring boot integration test facilities
Spring Boot集成测试设施
it says you can see up here i started my
它说你可以在这里看到我开始我的
integration tests on a random port so
在随机端口上进行集成测试，因此
that you know you don't conflict with
你知道你不会与之冲突
anything so i don't know it at startup
任何东西，所以我在启动时不知道
time but port the HTTP is going to
时间，但端口HTTP将
server is going to be running on so i
服务器将要运行，所以我
get that at runtime and then here you
在运行时得到它，然后在这里你
can see this is a simple server list
可以看到这是一个简单的服务器列表
implementation i don't know if you've
实施我不知道你是否
actually seen that 1i created a new
实际上看到1i创建了一个新的
class called static server list just
称为静态服务器列表的类
give them a list this server object is
给他们这个服务器对象的列表
from than as a netflix object but says
从比作为netflix对象，但说
hey just the only servers that are ever
嘿，仅此而已的服务器
going to come back from the server list
从服务器列表中返回
is localhost with this dynamic port and
是具有此动态端口的本地主机，并且
it allows you to test clients that use
它允许您测试使用
ribbon in integration tests been very
集成测试中的功能非常出色
useful for us without having a time yeah
没有时间对我们有用
without having a complete distributed
没有完整的分发
system right this is completely local to
系统权限，这完全是本地的
this integration test I'm going to run
我要运行此集成测试
within the same jvm I'm going to run a
在同一个JVM中，我要运行一个
service with HTTP m points and I'm any
HTTP m点的服务，我可以
client which is inside that which needs
内在需要的客户
to talk to a remote endpoint is always
与远程端点交谈总是
going to go to the same place it's
去同一个地方
actually just local here but you could
实际上只是本地的，但是你可以
imagine that you could you could go to a
想象你可以去
remote end point as well just by
远程端点也是如此
configuring it that way so we're
这样配置，我们
manipulating the client side load
处理客户端负载
balancer for fun and profit but to make
娱乐和利润的平衡器，但使
our lives easier at development time
在开发时我们的生活更轻松
basically you had it I have a demo for
基本上你有它，我有一个演示
this why don't you do that coachmans we
这就是为什么你不做那个车夫
actually had your laptop work let's see
确实让您的笔记本电脑工作了
we want to see this guy
我们想见这个家伙
make it fun now I can do that fairly
让它变得有趣，我现在可以公平地做到这一点
easily let me see so this is a fairly
轻松地让我看看，所以这是一个相当
simple spring boot app you can see i
简单的春季启动应用程序，你可以看到我
created this with the the start dots
用开始点创建了这个
spring die oh right the spring
春天死了，春天吧
initializer so i have the eureka client
初始化程序，所以我有尤里卡客户端
i also have the the ribbon starter web
我也有功能区入门网站
obviously actuator and a few others that
显然是执行器和其他一些
i will i will show you why they're
我会告诉你他们为什么
important here in a second to basic
在此基础上重要
endpoints since i'm just going to be a
端点，因为我只是要
client of myself i didn't want to write
我自己的客户，我不想写
two apps i was lazy and wrote one so i'm
我很懒的两个应用程序，写了一个，所以我
going to be a client to my the same app
将成为我同一个应用程序的客户
is going to just call itself so / home
会这样称呼自己/家
here is just going to call me so this
这里只是要打电话给我，所以这个
gives you an idea of how we've done
让您了解我们的工作方式
integration with the load balancer you
与您的负载均衡器集成
notice i don't have any well I do but
注意我做得不好，但是
I'm not using it right there in this
我没有在这里使用它
particular case i'm just using a normal
特殊情况下，我只是使用普通
rest template that spring cloud has this
其余模板，春云有这个
created for me but instead of using a
为我创建，而不是使用
fully qualified URL instead of a host
标准网址而不是主机
and port i have the service name which
和端口我有服务名称
if if i show you the configuration Dave
如果我向您显示配置Dave
showed you this last night in the demo
昨晚在演示中向您展示了
right it's the this is the name that
对，这就是这个名字
gets registered with service discovery
在服务发现中注册
with Eureka just called remedy mo okay
和尤里卡一起被称为补救措施
so and I just make a simple call 22 / me
所以，我打个简单的电话22 /我
and actually / me is using our discovery
实际上我正在使用我们的发现
client abstraction to get myself it
客户抽象让我自己
knows about itself and how it was
知道自己和如何
registered and the point is when you see
注册，关键是当你看到
here on me let me start a few of them on
在我这里，让我开始其中的一些
different ports so I've got
不同的端口，所以我有
these are all just running locally i
这些都只在本地运行
have a unique event Eureka is already
有一个独特的活动尤里卡已经
running here in the background right
在后台运行在这里
here so so I have these three different
在这里，所以我有这三个不同
services running now are they running on
现在正在运行的服务是否正在运行
random bullet had a heat that I just set
我刚刚设定的随机子弹发热
them up with static ports different ones
他们用不同的静态端口
run it at run time so you can see here
在运行时运行它，以便您可以在此处看到
is the Eureka dashboard just on my local
是我本地的Eureka仪表板
laptop and you can see I have three
笔记本电脑，你可以看到我有三个
ribbon demos running on on three
在三个上运行的功能区演示
different ports okay so now if I hit hit
不同的端口还可以，所以现在如果我命中
that endpoint on the first one 1991
1991年第一个端点
you'll see that it's it's cycling
您会发现它正在循环
through the three different services
通过三种不同的服务
just in random order now that's that's
只是随机排列，就是这样
just kind of the standard use case that
只是那种标准的用例
was bullet point zero eventually it
最终是零点
would hit the one that I'm interested
会击中我感兴趣的那个
had we registered it with with the
我们是否已向
tunnel for example the one that I'm
隧道，例如我
interested in well I thought well what
对好事感兴趣我想好了
can I do to actually make this this
我可以做这个吗
interesting so let's go back to the the
有趣，所以让我们回到
code here so I told you about the the
代码在这里，所以我告诉你有关
filters so I created a filter simply by
过滤器，所以我创建了一个过滤器
extending one of Netflix classes i use
扩展我使用的Netflix类之一
spring boots configuration properties i
春季靴子配置属性i
have this class called demo properties
具有此类的演示属性
simple demo namespace and a filter
简单的演示名称空间和过滤器
pattern this is based on springs what
模式是基于弹簧的
are they pattern matching utilities they
它们是模式匹配实用程序吗
take aunt like patterns yeah and again
像图案一样带阿姨
data there from from will get a plug-in
那里的数据将获得一个插件
for Baumbach so this filter says if
对于Baumbach，所以此过滤器会说
so given this list of servers right this
因此，鉴于此服务器列表
is a method I've overridden if my
是一种方法，如果我
property has a pattern I'm going to go
财产有我要去的模式
ahead and iterate through each server
前进并遍历每个服务器
and apply that pattern to the server ID
并将该模式​​应用于服务器ID
ID and if it matches I'm going to return
ID，如果匹配，我将返回
it ok so so how does that work so I'm
好的，那如何运作，所以我
going to take advantage of the spring
要利用春天
cloud being able to poke the spring
可以戳春天的云
environment wait they even still that's
环境等等，他们甚至仍然是
it a time where already yes this is yes
这是已经是的时候，这是肯定的
ready until yes thank you that yes so
准备好直到是，谢谢你，是的，所以
this is in the application itself right
这是在应用程序本身中
here so right there like I showed before
就像我之前展示的那样
here's my ribbon client and I've
这是我的缎带客户，我已经
installed if we go look at this ribbon
如果我们去看看这个丝带安装
demo configuration here is my demo
演示配置这是我的演示
server list filter and an interesting
服务器列表过滤器和一个有趣的
note here that was on the slide that I
请注意，这是我在幻灯片上
showed before I specifically had to
在我特别需要之前显示
remove the app configuration from here
从此处删除应用程序配置
because they was compiling the scanning
因为他们正在整理扫描
yes ah but you just put it in a
是的啊，但是你把它放在一个
different package and I know right
不同的包装，我知道是对的
component scanning my friends it's evil
扫描我的朋友这很邪恶
it's dangerous and I insurance and then
这很危险，我保险，然后
so why did we invent that I spent I
那为什么我们发明我花了我
spent a good half an hour trying to
花了一个半小时试图
figure out why the beans that this
弄清楚为什么豆子这样
particular one this client config bean
特定的一个此客户端配置bean
wasn't available when it started up and
在启动时不可用
I realized that I could have moved the
我意识到我本可以搬走
package or just turned off component
包装或刚刚关闭组件
scanning but I was lazy and just
扫描，但我很懒，只是
commented this out so so I've installed
评论了这个，所以我已经安装了
it it's this server list filter is in
这是服务器列表过滤器
each one of those demo apps that i was
我曾经的每个演示应用程序
already started up so now me
已经开始，所以现在我
make this side a little bigger we can
使这一面更大一点，我们可以
get it anybody's having trouble seeing
得到它，任何人都无法看到
that just shout and we can obviously
那只是大喊，我们显然可以
adjust nobody shouted they're all asleep
调整没人喊他们都睡着了
so so i'm using a let's get at all let's
所以我现在就让我们来吧
see so i'm using a little tool called
看到所以我正在使用一个叫做
HTTP i find it a little HTTP as its name
HTTP我发现它的名称有点HTTP
a little more friendly tool than curl
比卷曲更友好的工具
but the gist is i am going to make a
但要点是我要做出一个
post to 9999 t1 / m and i'm going to
发布到9999 t1 / m，我要
poke this this property the demo filter
戳此属性演示过滤器
pattern I'm just going to pass this this
模式我将通过这个
little hice name and poet yeah that's
小希瑟的名字和诗人是的
I'm just matching anything that ends in
我只是匹配任何以
in two and we'll see what happens here
一分为二，我们将看到这里发生的情况
and you can see the response says this
您可以看到响应说明
pattern this property was changed so now
模式此属性已更改，因此现在
if I come back to my little client here
如果我回到这里我的小客户
that was filtering through all three is
通过这三个过滤是
now stuck on nine to two so we just said
现在停留在九点到二点，所以我们只是说
if we go went back to that to this
如果我们去回到那个
picture I just said green clients go to
我刚才说绿色客户去
the red service you know with matching
您知道与匹配相匹配的红色服务
that pattern and that's interesting but
这种模式，这很有趣，但是
that affects everybody right because the
会影响到每个人，因为
way ribbon works and the way that server
功能区的工作方式以及服务器的方式
list filter works that gets cached and
列表过滤器可以缓存和
so it's running in a background thread
所以它在后台线程中运行
so you don't have access to any of the
因此您无权访问任何
user properties that you would like so
您想要的用户属性
this affects the whole service everyone
这影响到每个人的整体服务
will get that so now if like might be
会得到的，所以现在就好像
okay I mean depends really how you set
好吧，我的意思是取决于您的设置
your inspiration environment up right i
你的灵感环境就对了
mean i think there are two schools of
我的意思是我认为有两所学校
thought there I you either have a
以为我你有一个
developer has his own integration
开发人员有自己的集成
environment which is ideal but not
理想但不理想的环境
everybody has the resources yeah if you
每个人都有资源，如果你
had your own this would
有你自己的这个会
yeah work then it wouldn't matter anyway
是的，那就没关系了
oh you're sharing it with some other
哦，你正在和其他人分享
people i think that's well Spencer men
我认为很好的人Spencer men
when it affects he said it affects other
他说这会影响其他
people so other people might be
人，所以其他人可能是
developing their own service and they
发展自己的服务，他们
don't want to see your new throughout
不想看到整个
that physical yeah so I'm going to go
那个身体是的，所以我要去
ahead and reset that pattern to empty
向前并将该模式​​重置为空
and show a different one so my friend
并显示一个不同的，所以我的朋友
Rob what's rob's last name which which
抢劫的姓是什么
Rob spring session hey Rob winch winch
Rob spring session嘿，Rob winch绞盘
yes thank you sorry Rob Timmy rubs in a
是的，谢谢你，对不起，罗伯·蒂米（Rob Timmy）在
while yeah he had a he's done some great
是的，他做的很棒
things with spring session and so I
春天的事情，所以我
wanted to to get that in here as well so
也想在这里得到它
the the place where you can have access
您可以访问的地方
to user data to the basically the
将用户数据基本上
request thread is in the actual load
请求线程在实际负载中
balancer so i created my my own instance
平衡器，所以我创建了我自己的实例
of load balancer here so that I load
这里的负载均衡器的负载
balancer that's a ribbon thing right yep
平衡器是功能区是的
this is the the ribbon abstraction so
这是功能区的抽象
we're just saying anything of that type
我们只是在说那种话
in this context is going to get used yes
在这种情况下会习惯
and if we take a look at my load
如果我们看看我的负载
balancer so rather than using going to
平衡器，而不是使用
an environment properties I'm going to
我要去的环境属性
actually do two things I'm only going to
实际上要做两件事
show one in the interest of time but i'm
为了时间而显示一个，但是我
going to use spring session which is a
将使用春季会议这是一个
nice abstraction over an HTTP session it
通过HTTP会话进行漂亮的抽象
allows you to put data into some other
允许您将数据放入其他
data store to distribute your session in
数据存储以在其中分发会话
this case I'm going to use Redis and I'm
在这种情况下，我将使用Redis，
going to say if if this attribute has a
会说如果这个属性有一个
pattern in it similar to what i did with
模式类似于我所做的
the property except now i'm just getting
该物业，除了现在我只是
it from somewhere else right in a
它是从其他地方
different context and so the finale of
不同的背景，因此结局
thing if you're doing a session then
如果您正在做一个会议，那么
you're basically saying that each ease
您基本上是说每种轻松
it can have there
它可以在那里
patent right bingo so if I come like so
专利权宾果游戏，如果我这样来
I created a client again hosted my same
我再次创建了一个托管我的客户端
application but one of the things that
应用程序，但这是其中之一
Rob had just implemented was being able
罗伯刚刚实施的是能够
to find a session by a user ID so you
通过用户ID查找会话，因此您
could potentially have some user
可能有一些用户
interface or API that says hey give me
嘿的接口或API给我
the session for user x that is logged
用户x记录的会话
into your system and you know for me and
进入您的系统，您对我和
then we can we can find it so this time
然后我们可以找到它，所以这次
I'm going to so that's basically all
我要说的基本上就是全部
this little API here is is to set that
这个小API是用来设置
attribute for my session i've already
我已经拥有的会话属性
logged in so i'm going to set it to two
登录，所以我将其设置为两个
three instead and so now we come back
三个代替，所以现在我们回来
here and instead of going to two it's
在这里，而不是去两个
going to three but so if we want to
要三点，但是如果我们想
prove a point right we'll come excuse me
证明一点正确，我们会过来对不起
you can copy this come to a new browser
您可以将其复制到新的浏览器
that has no session right Logan is a
没有会话权限的Logan是一个
tiffany either yeah login again
蒂芙尼或者是再次登录
basically the same user with a different
基本上是同一用户，但不同
session so I'm just going off a session
会议，所以我只是去参加一个会议
ID not necessarily user ID but that like
ID不一定是用户ID，而是类似
I said that could happen with the new
我说过，新的
API is the rob has created so now you
API是抢劫犯创建的，所以现在您
can see that in this session I am going
可以看到在本次会议中我要去
through all the three going through the
通过所有三个经历
normal cycle in the back here in my
在我后面的正常循环中
session I only get the one right so this
会议上我只有一个正确的，所以这个
could be how we could route back to just
可能就是我们如何回到
me in a totally shared environment where
我在完全共享的环境中
different users how I didn't have that
不同的用户我没有那个
static patent that use that earlier up
较早使用的静态专利
did you cleared it that I cleared it
你清除了吗我清除了
yeah yep so so there's some fun with
是的，所以有一些乐趣
ribbon I really enjoyed doing this
我真的很喜欢这样做
because I've for a year I've been saying
因为我已经说了一年了
you can do this kind of stuff with
你可以用这种东西
ribbon it's super flexible and it was
色带，它超级灵活，而且
fun to actually I think you know where
有趣的是，我想你知道哪里
we're heading with that to be clear is
我们要前进的是要清楚的是
we'll probably make some off the shelf
我们可能会现成的
you know server lists and filters so you
您知道服务器列表和过滤器，因此您
can just use and probably ones that the
可以使用，可能
tooling knows about in fact so we can
工具实际上知道，所以我们可以
probably help the tooling guys to guide
可能会帮助工具指导
the developer experience here so that in
开发人员的经验，以便
the spring boot dashboard you'll be able
Spring Boot仪表板，您将能够
to
至
run your app locally yeah regstrate
是的，请在本地运行您的应用
with a remote server and also register
与远程服务器并注册
and you happened for the for the for the
而你却为
ribbon right just for completeness I
丝带只是为了完整性我
actually had I wasn't running the random
其实我不是在随机运行
or round-robin rule it was running a
或循环规则，它正在运行
weighted response time rule right so
加权响应时间规则正确
this is how you could plug in a
这是您可以插入
different load balancing algorithm into
不同的负载均衡算法
ribbon because that's a pretty common
功能区，因为这很常见
question how do you change that so is
问你如何改变呢
that a fan of one that comes yes this
那个来的粉丝
isn't this this weighted response time
这不是这个加权的响应时间
is calm down that fix calm down Netflix
冷静下来让Netflix冷静下来
yep so ribbon where were we about here
是的，所以功能区我们在这里
okay so that brings us to a new topic
好的，这样就把我们带到了一个新的话题
ready and any questions before we move
在我们出发之前准备好任何问题
on yes one bill
在一张账单上
yeah so the question is question is does
是的，所以问题是
that rule does the rule that we just set
该规则执行我们刚刚设置的规则
up apply to all services that we're
应用于我们提供的所有服务
contacting or just the one and the
联系或只是一个和
answer is it depends so in that
答案是因为这取决于
particular case that rule was specific
特定规则的特殊情况
to my ribbon demo client ribbon client
到我的功能区演示客户端功能区客户端
but if you you can set a default
但是如果您可以设置默认值
configuration for every ribbon client
每个功能区客户端的配置
and that one could be used so you can
并且可以使用一个，这样您就可以
set up a default rule for all your
为您所有的人设置默认规则
clients but it's from a client
客户，但来自客户
perspective right not from yeah when you
正确的观点不是来自当你
say it's confusing for me I sleep when
说对我来说我感到困惑
you say ribbon client you really mean
你说的是丝带客户
the service that you want to contact
您要联系的服务
right so that if there's a global
正确的，如果有一个全球
default that applies to all service
适用于所有服务的默认值
downstream services and then for each
下游服务，然后每个
one you can do what's been suggested as
一个你可以做的建议
well write an override it right but it's
好吧写一个覆盖它吧，但是
from a client perspective right you
从客户角度来说，您
don't configure the algorithm on the
不要在
instances you can figure it on the
实例，您可以在
client that wants to contact those
想要联系那些客户
instances that makes sense yeah as
是有意义的实例
ribbon is ribbon is a client side load
功能区是功能区是客户端负载
balance or right that's where it lives
平衡或正确的地方
it doesn't live in front of the
它不存在于
instances it lives on the client who is
实例存在于客户
trying to contact those those instances
试图联系那些实例
okay right so the question is it doesn't
好吧，所以问题是
it's not actually not relevant to
它实际上与
whether Eureka is secure or not but
尤里卡是否安全，但是
could you just bypass Eureka completely
你能完全绕过尤里卡吗
and go to a fixed server if you wanted
并转到固定服务器（如果需要）
to well yeah right because it's just a
是的，因为这只是一个
list yeah I could have a list as a
是的，我可以列出一个
server list you get part of it from
您从中获得服务器列表的一部分
Eureka you get a part of it from a fix
尤里卡（Eureka），您可以从修复中受益
instead of a pattern-matching servers i
而不是模式匹配服务器
got from eureka it could have just been
从尤里卡那里得到的可能只是
a server right and if that attribute was
服务器权限，如果该属性是
there just go to whatever the attribute
只要去任何属性
value is right certainly it's just a
价值是正确的，当然这只是一个
server list it doesn't have to come from
服务器列表，它不一定来自
a service registry I think is really the
我认为确实是一个服务注册表
answer to the question
回答问题
it's not yet so the question is what
还没有，所以问题是
about the IDE what's available in
关于IDE的可用内容
different IDs for that so SDS has got
为此有不同的ID，因此SDS
some some way towards that like I'm
一些类似的方法
saying we're guiding the tools team
说我们正在指导工具团队
towards a picture like this what what
对这样的图片
they have in sts is that basic green red
他们在STS中是基本的绿色红色
with the yellow proxy in the middle
中间有黄色代理
intellij haven't started work on that
intellij尚未就此开展工作
yet but I know what they're like white
但我知道他们像白人
as soon as they see what's an STI still
一旦他们看到了什么是性传播感染
probably have it out within a few days
可能在几天之内
so they haven't done that yet yeah I
所以他们还没那么做
know of so so the next topic yeah so
知道所以下一个话题
it's always changing gears of a look so
它总是在改变外观
I mean we've I actually like the kind of
我的意思是我们真的很喜欢
approaches that we've just been talking
我们一直在谈论的方法
about where I get to develop stuff
关于我在哪里开发东西
locally but it actually interacts in an
但实际上它在一个
integration setting with a more or less
集成设置或多或少
alive real system I like that way of
我喜欢那种活着的真实系统
working some people like to do things in
工作一些人喜欢做事
a bit differently and so they they also
有点不同，所以他们也
like to to think about the g-word right
想思考正确的g字
governance and that's when you start to
治理，那就是您开始
think about contracts right and you
想好合同，你
consumer-driven what's the term oh I can
消费者驱动的术语是什么，我可以
never remember can't see me driven
永远不记得看不到我开车
contract yes oh yeah so the idea where
合同是的，是的，这样的想法在哪里
that is that fundamentally you can avoid
那就是从根本上你可以避免
a lot of that you know the mess that we
很多你知道我们一团糟
were just talking about which is a mess
只是在谈论那是一团糟
I'll agree I'll admit but the nice thing
我同意我会承认，但是好东西
is that it ends up with me interacting
最终是与我互动
with a real system locally you can avoid
在本地使用真实系统，您可以避免
that to a large extent and people do
人们在很大程度上
right our friends are for finance of
对，我们的朋友是为了
really big on this and we'll show you
在这方面非常重要，我们将向您展示
that their tool set in a minute that
他们的工具在一分钟内完成
Spencer's got a nice demo the
Spencer的演示很不错
alternative is to think about what it
另一种方法是考虑一下
means for a quiet for a producer and a
对于生产者和
consumer of let's just call them
我们的消费者就叫他们
messages for now it doesn't even have to
消息现在甚至都不需要
be HTTP it could be any any kind of
是HTTP，可以是任何一种
exchange but typically we're talking
交流，但通常我们在谈论
about HTTP for the examples we're going
关于HTTP的示例
to show here what does it mean to have a
在这里展示拥有一个
contract between those two things and
这两件事之间的契约
what can you change without breaking
您可以改变什么而又不中断
your
你的
Seema's that's really what it comes down
Seema就是这样
to isn't it and that's why it's the g4
是不是，这就是为什么它是g4
governance so there you know the high
治理，所以在那里你知道高
level there are some fairly different
级别有一些相当不同
approaches to this as well so maybe I
方法，所以也许我
don't know these DC or slides and maybe
不知道这些DC或幻灯片，也许
you could talk about those it well so so
你可以很好地谈论这些
for example in the it was just kind of
例如，在
glossed over a little bit but in in the
掩饰了一点，但在
they talked about it didn't in the
他们谈论它不在
keynote last night right that the UI had
UI昨晚的主题演讲
been developed with the stub right with
与存根一起开发
the service and I believe you used
服务，我相信你曾经
spring MVC such animates that and and
春天MVC这样动画和
basically you created the spring MVC app
基本上，您创建了spring MVC应用程序
but all it did was return the contents
但它所做的只是返回内容
of adjacent file as a string as a simple
一个字符串作为一个简单的相邻文件
stub right so it's an actual running
存根对，所以这是实际运行
service it's real Java code but it
服务它是真正的Java代码，但它
doesn't really it just returns a static
真的不只是返回静态
list of data right that's a simple way
数据权限列表，这是一种简单的方法
that's one particular way to do a stub
那是做存根的一种特殊方法
and that's one of those when when's the
当那是什么时候
service that you want to contact doesn't
您要联系的服务没有
exist yet in a Greenfield situation like
存在于未开发的环境中
like they had oh it doesn't exist in the
就像他们拥有的哦，它不存在
form that you once it's a which is an
形式，一旦你是一个是一个
initiation i came across fellow right
启蒙我碰到同伴权利
you've got a legacy system you want to
您有想要的旧系统
interact with it so you want to define a
与之互动，因此您想定义一个
contract with it but you don't actually
与它签约，但你实际上并没有
have the endpoints in place yet so you
有了端点，所以您
build a stub so just so you can get some
建立一个存根，以便您可以得到一些
velocity going right that's what that
速度向右走就是那个
was a scenario we had for the keynote
这是我们主题演讲的场景
which is actually you know in practice
实际上你在实践中知道
quite calm and I find that people
相当平静，我发现人们
develop quite large sections of systems
开发相当大的系统部分
without actually having live data in the
而实际上没有实时数据
back of it and that works yeah and
它的背面，是的，是的，
another situation you come up with is
你想到的另一种情况是
you have all your services and in one
您拥有所有服务，合而为一
case will show you they have actually
案例会告诉你他们实际上已经
published stubs somewhere that you can
您可以在某个地方发布的存根
use to verify the interaction with those
用于验证与那些人的互动
other services without actually having
其他服务实际上没有
to stand up all those services like dave
站起来像戴夫一样的所有服务
was describing yeah you basically have a
在描述是的，你基本上有一个
stub system around your client that you
客户周围的存根系统
interact with the stubs on the on the
与上的存根进行交互
other side so instead of having a live
另一面，所以没有生活
integration system you just there is a
集成系统，您只是有一个
system it's a party that you want to
系统，这是您想要参加的聚会
join but you can join it in a sort of
加入，但您可以加入一种
mocked way I'm not not in a real way
嘲弄我不是真正的方式
yeah so
所以啊
higher level than then using you know
比使用您知道的更高的水平
mockito or easy mock or something like
模拟或简单模拟或类似的东西
that you're still you know going over
你还是你知道要过去
the wire yeah but lower level than
电线是的，但水平低于
having a full system up and running and
拥有完整的系统并运行
we've seen a number of different tools
我们已经看到了许多不同的工具
and approaches used to this as well so I
以及用于此的方法，所以我
was actually just talking to a client
其实只是在跟客户说话
last week where we were arguing the
上周我们在争论
debate about this first bullet point so
关于第一个要点的辩论，所以
which should you do and I didn't think
你应该怎么做，我没想到
there's a right answer so I'll just
有一个正确的答案，所以我就
explain both approaches one of them is
解释这两种方法之一是
to it's for your producers right to to
是为了您的制作人有权
publish their contract and say right I'm
发表合同，说对了
a service I'm service a this is what I
我正在服务的服务这就是我的服务
look like and published that as some
看起来像并发布了一些
sort of stubble thing that other people
别人讨厌的东西
can use and that's the approach that
可以使用的方法就是
Spencer is going to demo in a minute I
Spencer马上要演示
think the other foot the other way of
用另一种方式思考另一只脚
doing they're looking at it is kind of
他们正在看的时候有点
upside down completely and actually
完全颠倒过来
don't I don't like this but I've seen
不，我不喜欢，但是我已经看过
people I've seen people doing it this is
我见过的人正在这样做
why we were talking about it last week
为什么我们上周在谈论它
where the consumers of my service
我服务的消费者
published their integration tests
发布了他们的集成测试
against my service and I have to run
违反我的服务，我必须逃跑
them that's why I don't like it because
他们就是为什么我不喜欢它，因为
it puts the eyes on me I think that's
它把目光投向我，我认为那是
too much friction but that's sort of a
摩擦太大，但这有点
higher level of governance if you like
如果您愿意，可以提高治理水平
that's a stronger guarantee that when I
更有力的保证，当我
publish my service is it's definitely
发布我的服务肯定是
going to work because if you know if
去上班，因为如果你知道
they if they didn't write their test the
他们，如果他们不写他们的测试
right way that's their fault but they
正确的方式是他们的错，但他们
they're only telling me what they're
他们只是告诉我他们是什么
going to do by by publishing their tests
通过发布他们的测试来完成
so that's a different way of doing it
所以这是另一种方式
yep and we'll look at one particular
是的，我们来看一个特别的
actually a couple of different ways I
实际上我有几种不同的方式
kind of tweaked the way that the for
有点调整了
finance guys generate their their
财务人员产生他们的
producer stubs using a queue rest and
生产者存根使用队列休息和
wire mock and then thank you added the
电线模拟，然后谢谢你添加了
ability for jay is another one that I've
周杰伦的能力是我的另一项能力
come across this and it's a bit like why
碰到这个，这有点像为什么
I'm off basically I mean it's you know
我离开了，我的意思是你知道
it's a yam all declar declarative yeah
都是山药，全部是声明性的
more thing you just declare what the
你只是声明更多的东西
stubs should look like and they can get
存根看起来应该很像
the data from different files and I
来自不同文件的数据，我
think there's some sort of basic state
认为有某种基本状态
machine features in there as well and
那里的机器功能以及
I'd also like just to mention like
我也想提一下
Spencer saying the keynote last night we
斯宾塞昨晚在我们的主题演讲中
were using spring MVC and that's
使用Spring MVC，那是
actually a perfectly good way to produce
实际上是一种完美的生产方式
imple stubs it's just as good as the
简单的存根和
simple uses of those other things it's
这些其他东西的简单用法
just that the thing that you can't do
只是你做不到的事情
very easily with any of this actually is
这很容易，实际上是
is real stateful I'm stuff so if you're
是真正的有状态的我，所以如果你是
sending a message to a service and you
向服务发送消息，您
expect it to change your state as a
希望它能改变您的状态
response as a result and then you want
结果是响应，然后您想要
to test that state with another another
与另一个国家测试该状态
call that's going to be challenging for
通话将具有挑战性
a stub so that's actually wear it often
一个存根，所以实际上经常穿
falls down I think anyway so we're going
跌倒了，我想无论如何我们要走了
to show you a bunch of these things
给你看一堆这些东西
there's also the whole thing about
还有整个事情
whether the stubs are running in in the
存根是否正在运行
same process as your tests or whether
与测试相同的过程，或者是否
you run them remotely as you know
您可以远程运行它们
individual services or maybe as a single
个别服务，或者作为一个服务
service that marks everything yep and
标记一切的服务
the tools from for finance allow either
财务工具允许
i'm going to show embedded stubs in fact
我实际上将展示嵌入式存根
so the kind of the general pattern that
所以那种一般的模式
i'm going to use for doing these these
我将用来做这些
brownfield stubs which uses wire mock
使用电线模拟的布朗菲尔德存根
and i'm going to show two different ways
我将展示两种不同的方式
to generate the the JSON file for what
为什么生成JSON文件
for wire mock using they showed spring
用于电线模拟，他们展示了春天
rest docks yesterday so i'm actually
昨天休息，所以我实际上
going to show how to use rest docks to
将展示如何使用休息码头
generate the stub so along with your
生成存根，以便与您一起
test comes the stub or you accurist has
测试来了存根或您的指控者有
a groovy dsl that they use the for
他们使用的常规dsl
finance guys are pretty heavily involved
财务人员参与度很高
in accurist i don't know if they run it
在Accurist中，我不知道他们是否运行它
but they think not see that he does it
但他们认为没有看到他这样做
is that his project okay okay so so they
是他的项目好吧好吧，所以他们
let they like this and it's a groovy dsl
让他们喜欢这个，这是一个普通的dsl
and i'll show you a little bit of that
我会告诉你一点
but once those stubs are generated wire
但是一旦这些存根生成了
mock loads those stubs up and runs a
模拟加载那些存根并运行
service the the stub runner i actually
服务我真正的存根
have registers so here we're going to
有寄存器，所以在这里我们要
actually transition from eureka as a
实际上从尤里卡过渡为
service registry and it's and discovery
服务注册表及其发现
to zookeeper so you'll get a little bit
给动物园管理员，所以你会得到一点
of that that you guys show that night
你们那天晚上展示的那个
today I'm gonna we had that you with it
今天我要和你在一起
awesome again you'll get more thursday
再次很棒，您将在星期四得到更多
on zookeeper but it's the stubs actually
在动物园管理员上，但实际上是存根
get registered in zookeeper and the
在Zookeeper中注册并
client when it it behaves normally it
客户端，当它正常运行时
just says hey zookeeper give me a
只是说嘿，动物园管理员给我一个
service x and zookeeper returns the host
服务X和Zookeeper返回主机
and port of the stub and then it makes
和存根的端口，然后它使
its normal call so it's pretty slick
它的正常通话，因此非常漂亮
little integration where the stubs
存根很少整合
actually registered with service
实际在服务中注册
discovery yeah you could you could but
发现是的，你可以，但是
the zoo cuso4 finances donated a lot of
动物园cuso4财政捐赠了很多
our zookeeper code and so they have some
我们的动物园管理员代码，所以他们有一些
of the stuff already built for zookeeper
已经为动物园管理员建造的东西
generalized a little bit and it could be
泛化了一点，这可能是
made available I think it is yeah yeah
提供，我认为是的，是的
more available to another service he's
他可以使用其他服务
probably got time to do this em equipe
大概有时间做这个装备
but we get fan let's just look at a
但是我们得到粉丝，让我们来看看
five-foot full the different sure so
五英尺满的肯定如此
this is a sample of the acuras DSL I
这是acuras DSL I的示例
don't know that we need to get into it
不知道我们需要参与其中
too much but so this says at URL foo
太多，但这在URL foo上说
with the HTTP method get this is what
与HTTP方法得到这是什么
the response should look like I'm just
响应应该看起来像我
going to return the simple value for
将要返回的简单值
that's gravy the I ain t amo yep
这是肉汁，我是不是
whatever yeah so spring rest Doc's right
是的，所以春天休息Doc的权利
that they showed yesterday is very just
他们昨天展示的非常公正
the generic way except i created a new
通用的方式，除了我创建了一个新的
snippet here that says snippet is a rest
片段在这里说片段是休息
of thing right yes so not only what they
是的，所以不仅是他们
do is they when you run your tests it
他们是在您运行测试时吗
generates example requests and responses
生成示例请求和响应
right here you include in the
在这里，您将
documentation they'll sniff it and
文档，他们会嗅探它，
there's a certain format that the sniff
有一种特定的格式
it has to have right so it's just plain
它必须有权利，所以这很简单
text or it's got you know in this case
文字或在这种情况下知道
some wrap around it yeah so I I created
一些包裹它是的，所以我创建了
for this demo something called the wire
在这个演示中，称为线的东西
mocks dub snippet that could eventually
模仿配音片段，最终可能
make it out to something more generally
使它更普遍
available and then instead of using the
可用，然后代替使用
dsl you describe what this should look
DSL您描述这应该看起来
like so / foo is a Jason she returned
像这样/ foo是她回来的杰森
okay and we're going to go ahead and
好的，我们将继续
dock
码头
meant foo team oh yeah and this is what
是指foo队，哦，是的，这就是
ends up getting generated using either
最终使用任一生成
of those methods just to show you this
这些方法只是为了向您展示
is the format wire mock expects of
是模拟模拟期望的格式
course you could have just written this
当然你可以写这个
right is one way to do it just right the
正确是做到这一点的一种方法
wire mocks tub in the JSON right
JSON右侧的模拟电线浴缸
everybody likes to edit Jason right yeah
每个人都喜欢编辑Jason对吧
I I personally have when i did this i
我个人有我这样做的时候我
really wanted to get the rest docks
我真的很想让其余的码头
working because i generally like this
工作，因为我通常喜欢这样
yeah because as your application changes
是的，因为随着您的应用程序的更改
it's going to break your test and you'd
它会破坏你的测试，你会
have to go in and fix it the stub gets
必须去修复它，存根得到
updated things happen in a more
更新的事情发生在更多
automated fashion so this would be
自动化的时尚，所以这将是
something that for spring MVC right so /
对Spring MVC来说是正确的，所以/
locations in fact this is it's a fairly
位置实际上这是一个相当
using this is exactly what you're known
使用这个正是您所知道的
okay but it's just a simple spring MVC
好的，但这只是一个简单的Spring MVC
forward to a static resource yep very
是非常静态的
simple you can do get some posts just a
很简单，您可以获得一些帖子
little bit more challenge to do anything
做任何事情都有更多挑战
yeah some of the some of the more
是的，更多一些
complicated interactions like anything
像任何事物一样复杂的交互
stay filled it it works pretty well yup
保持填充它工作很好
for simple cases okay so you can
对于简单的情况还可以，所以您可以
probably do your air case this is what
可能你的航空箱是这样的
it's about right yes so so this stub
是的，是的，所以这个存根
rudder from for finance what happens is
来自金融的方向舵会发生什么
during your build the wire mocks tub
在构建期间，电线模拟盆
gets generated it gets packaged into a
生成后，打包成一个
zip file or jar file i don't remember
我不记得的zip文件或jar文件
and then published to nexus so for
然后发布到连结
finance uses this internally they
财务内部使用它们
publish all their stubs so that every
发布所有存根，以便每个
consumer of all these applications just
所有这些应用程序的使用者
knows where to get where to get their
知道从哪里得到他们的
stubs so the stub runner comes up and
存根，以便存根运行器出现，
there is a i will show you the list of
有一个AI将显示给您列表
dependency each service so in general
通常依赖每个服务
the way we have done service clients you
我们为客户提供服务的方式
don't have to know up front what I'm a
不必事先知道我是什么
consumer of right you just at runtime
您在运行时才是权利的使用者
you say I need to contact you know the
你说我需要联系你知道
red service
红色服务
but for this to work you have to list
但是要工作，您必须列出
your dependencies in the application dot
您对应用程序点的依赖
properties or gamma file that says I'm a
属性或伽玛文件说我是
consumer of red so that stub runner
红色的消费者，使存根
knows which can switch dependencies to
知道哪些可以将依赖关系切换到
go get from from nexus and then like I
从关系中得到，然后像我一样
said it will spin up a wire mock server
说它将启动一个有线模拟服务器
for each dependency and then register
对于每个依赖项，然后注册
those servers in service discovery so
这些服务器在服务发现中
let's go see it happen this was actually
让我们去看看这确实是
good if we were to use Dave laptops we
好，如果我们要使用戴夫笔记本电脑，我们
wouldn't have been able to do this demo
不可能做这个演示
so one demo was going to not work today
所以一个演示今天将无法正常工作
and we can't was it was his yeah so so i
我们不能是那是他，所以我
have just at a real high level this
才有真正的高水平
simple application there's two providers
简单的应用程序有两个提供程序
a food provider and a bar provider yeah
食物提供者和酒吧提供者
I know I can't actually on that side so
我知道我实际上不能站在那一边
I'm just going to tell you there's
我只想告诉你
there's two providers in one consumer
一个消费者中有两个提供商
let me show you the the application yamo
让我向您展示应用程序yamo
so this is the foo consumer
所以这是foo消费者
configuration oh sorry and so here's
配置哦，抱歉，这是
this list of dependency so foo consumer
这个依赖列表，所以foo消费者
depends on food provider and bar
取决于食物供应商和酒吧
provider ok that's the topology consumer
好的，这是拓扑使用者
with two providers and some some
有两个提供商和一些
configuration for for stub runner so if
存根运行器的配置，如果
i run this guy he's actually already
我经营这个人，他实际上已经
running so he's going to actually run
跑步，所以他实际上会跑步
something in process so which will stub
正在处理的东西，将存根
base at those foo and bar providers
以那些foo和bar提供者为基础
right yeah so what is it what actually
是的，那实际上是什么
is happening when this starts up because
当它开始时正在发生，因为
zookeepers java-based it's actually
基于Java的zookeepers实际上
starting the service discovery provider
启动服务发现提供程序
is starting each stub and then starting
开始每个存根，然后开始
the consumer actual consumer application
消费者实际的消费者应用
so I actually
所以我实际上
wrote hey let's see what Porter why I'm
写了嘿，让我们看看波特为什么我
here 80 81 okay
这里80 81好
so I actually thought this would be I
所以我实际上以为会是我
wrote my own I wrote an actuator
自己写我写了一个执行器
endpoint for the stub runner that says
表示结果的存根运行器的端点
hey what stubs have you started so we
嘿，你开始了什么存根，所以我们
can see that food provider is on
可以看到食物提供者在
localhost 14 blah blah blah and bar
本地主机14等等等等等等
providers on some other random port
其他随机端口上的提供程序
right so this gives me a little
对，所以这给了我一点
visibility into the stubs and so now i
存根的可见性，所以现在我
can hit hit my local consumer and these
可以打我本地的消费者，这些
values came from the stub whose yep
值来自其是的存根
envira tentacle yes yeah five and again
环境触手是的，是的，五遍又一遍
with the other dependency the consumer
与其他依赖性消费者
application if we want to take a look at
如果我们想看一下应用程序
it I have a separate consumer service
我有单独的消费者服务
here when I called foos it simply went
当我打电话给foos时，它就走了
to food provider / booze and so it was a
给食品提供者/酒，所以这是一个
real rest template call just to the
真正的休息模板调用只
steps right so this this application was
步骤正确，因此此应用程序是
running in total isolation including the
完全隔离地运行，包括
service provider and and the stubs
服务提供商和存根
running dynamically so this is something
动态运行，所以这是东西
that if if the for finance guys here
如果如果这里的财务人员
were they would they love working with
他们愿意与他们合作吗
this style of okay of stubs just sit
这种样式的存根就坐
through a few okay yeah and then so we
通过一些好吧，然后我们
got in the last 10 minutes we've got a
在最近10分钟内
whole other set of topics basically
基本上其他全部主题
about topics around you know if you make
关于你周围的话题，你知道你是否
a change locally how quickly can you get
在本地进行更改，您有多快
it deployed and in action so that the
它已经部署并付诸行动，以便
sort of broad sub sub topic is hot
广泛的子子主题很热门
reloading and code swapping and then a
重新加载和代码交换，然后
number of different ways of doing this
多种不同的方式
right so there are already in in most
对，所以大多数已经有
IDEs although IntelliJ he seemed to seem
IDEs，尽管他似乎是IntelliJ
to find this very difficult jvm hot-swap
找到这个非常困难的jvm热插拔
has been a feature since like java 1.6 i
自从像Java 1.6 i以来一直是一个功能
think or maybe is on
想或者也许正在
on point six I think which means if you
在第六点，我认为这意味着
make a class change and it didn't change
改变班级并没有改变
the signature of a method then the JVM
方法的签名，然后是JVM
can just replace it and the the IDS will
可以更换它，而IDS将
happily do that for you so you can
开心地为您做，这样您就可以
continue to work I use that feature all
继续工作，我全部使用该功能
the time also I mean it also means that
时间也是我的意思，这也意味着
you can generally speaking reload static
您通常可以重装静态
resources like you know HTML stylesheet
您熟悉的HTML样式表资源
stuff I that that's the bit that the
东西我那就是那个
IntelliJ users have trouble with for
IntelliJ用户在使用时遇到麻烦
some reason the clips just seems to do
剪辑似乎确实有某些原因
it then ok the next level up that's so I
然后确定下一个级别，所以我
think I think Phil might be talking
认为我认为菲尔可能在说话
about dev tools in more detail but I
关于开发工具的更多细节，但我
very briefly mentioned it last night I'm
昨晚我很简短地提到了
not sure we're going to have time to
不确定我们是否有时间
look at it in any detail spring boot 1.3
详细查看一下spring boot 1.3
ships with a new new library called dev
附带了一个新的名为dev的新库
tools so if you include that on your
工具，如果您将其包含在自己的工具中
classpath it basically gives you a
它基本上给你一个classpath
couple of new features one of which is
几个新功能之一是
it it monitors for the classpath and if
它监视类路径，如果
you make a change to a class now you can
您现在可以更改班级了
do anything right so now you can create
做正确的事情，所以现在您可以创建
a new class or you could create a new
新课，也可以创建一个新课
method or you could change a method
方法，或者您可以更改方法
signature and do anything then it will
签名，然后做任何事情，它将
the IDE generally speaking is just going
一般而言，IDE只是在运行
to recompile that and the challenge then
重新编译，然后挑战
is to get it into a live deployment and
是将其投入实时部署
so what the dev tools do is they use a
因此，开发人员工具使用的是
class later trick to basically throw
上课以后的技巧基本上是扔
away the old class load the new one and
离开旧班级，加载新班级，
then actually restart the whole spring
然后实际上重新启动整个春天
application context and that might sound
应用程序上下文，这可能听起来
like a drastic thing to do it is a bit
像做一件大事一样有点
but it turns out that it's a lot faster
但事实证明它要快得多
than you think it might be because for
比您想象的要大
instance you know if I'm running
实例，你知道我是否在跑步
hibernate is hibernate doesn't have to
休眠是休眠，不必
get reloaded it's only the application
重新加载它只是应用程序
classes so hibernate can just stay warm
上课让冬眠可以保持温暖
and it doesn't take so long to reload
并不需要很长时间重新加载
the spring application context of that
那个春天的应用程序上下文
itself isn't very isn't very resource
本身不是很不是资源
intensive the other thing it comes with
密集的另一件事
is the single live reload which is a
是单次实时重载
thing on the internet just google it and
互联网上的东西只是用谷歌搜索
you for that you get a browser plugin
为此，您获得了一个浏览器插件
which you know isn't anything to do with
你知道跟这无关
us but you install that and your browser
我们，但您安装了它，然后使用了浏览器
and what it does is it like it reloads
它所做的是像重新加载一样
the browser so if you're you're
浏览器，所以如果您是
no visiting a website which you're
禁止访问您所访问的网站
developing locally it's basically
在本地发展基本上
detecting changes the IDE is detecting
检测IDE正在检测的更改
the changes but then its broadcasting
变化，然后广播
those to your browser plugin and so
那些到您的浏览器插件，等等
there's a protocol for that which is
有一个协议是
called live reload and that works really
称为实时重新加载，这确实有效
well SDS supports all this stuff kind of
SDS支持所有这些东西
quite natively now so the the especially
现在相当本地化
the live reload it's a little bit fiddly
实时重新加载有点麻烦
to set up you've got to run a separate
要进行设置，您必须单独运行
sidecar process it tells you how to do
边车过程告诉您如何做
that and this bring boot documentation
那带来了启动文档
but SDS just does it right so you can if
但是SDS只是做对了，所以您可以
you have devtools on your classpath sts
你的classpath sts上有devtools
detects that and just does everything
检测到并完成所有操作
for you the next level is spring-loaded
对您来说下一个层次是弹簧式的
which is a java agent that we built but
这是我们构建的Java代理，但是
don't use that much grails uses it j
不要使用太多的grails使用它
hipster uses it we showed what they were
赶时髦的人使用它，我们向他们展示了
doing to yoga and he kind of flipped his
做瑜伽，他有点翻转
lid so so we haven't pushed it all that
盖，所以我们还没有全部推开
hard it's a java agent technology and it
难，这是Java代理技术，
works for a limited class of spring
适用于春季限量课程
reloading problems basically and then
基本上重新加载问题，然后
you've got the basically the
你基本上有
professional standard which is j rebel
专业标准是j rebel
if you can afford to buy it it's
如果你买得起的话
definitely worth it because it does save
绝对值得，因为它确实可以节省
a lot of time if you're doing a lot of
很多时间，如果您正在做很多事情
different things in those about spring
关于春天的那些不同的事情
and it knows how to reload stuff without
它知道如何重新加载东西而无需
starting the couple starting the
开始夫妻开始
application context again basically okay
应用上下文再次基本还可以
so we've just got some diagrams that
所以我们有一些图
show how some of those thing work things
展示其中一些东西如何运作
work the hot reloading locally so just
在本地工作热装
to making a change and then restarting
进行更改，然后重新启动
the application context that's the dev
作为开发人员的应用程序上下文
tools next one is dev tools with the
下一个工具是带有
browser plugins so the browser plugins
浏览器插件，因此浏览器插件
now listening to a sidecar and the
现在正在听边车，
sidecar pushes the change and the
边车推动变革，
browser reloads through a plug-in and
浏览器通过插件重新加载，
then the last thing which is really cool
那么最后一件事真的很酷
which I really did one to demo a we
我真的做了一个演示我们
don't have time be my laptop not
没有时间做我的笔记本电脑
connected but I'll I'll demo it to
已连接，但我将演示给
anybody actually later on probably
后来有人可能
tomorrow would be better because I've
明天会更好，因为我
got other two presentations now today
今天有另外两个演讲
and then to go and get ready for them
然后去为他们做准备
but STS in particular lets you do this
但特别是STS可以让您做到这一点
with also remote debugging so this live
与远程调试，所以这直播
this
这个
client app that sidecar the facilitator
辅助应用程序的客户端应用程序
live reload also can act as a tunnel for
实时重新加载也可以充当隧道
remote debugger and so you can have a
远程调试器，因此您可以拥有一个
process running in Cloud Foundry you set
您设置的Cloud Foundry中运行的流程
a breakpoint in it and your local code
其中的断点和您的本地代码
you hit the no service remotely and it
您远程击中了无服务
actually breaks it's very slow this
实际上打破了这很慢
remote debugging so it's the last resort
远程调试，所以这是最后的手段
but it actually is easy to set up with
但实际上很容易设置
SCS next one right so actually that was
SCS的下一项权利实际上是
that topic finished and then we just
这个话题结束了，然后我们就
wanted to have a few words at the end of
想要在末尾说几句话
our how do you as a developer how do you
我们如何作为开发人员
sort of interact with the application
与应用程序进行某种交互
lifecycle and that's where the AL is and
生命周期，这就是AL所在的位置
alm management and some you know some
高层管理，有些你知道一些
cloud native messages for that basically
基本上为此而生的本机消息
so this ad hoc deployment and mixed
所以这个临时部署和混合
local remote that I've been talking
我一直在谈论的本地遥控器
about I like it as a development time
关于我喜欢它作为开发时间
thing but it's also always going to be
东西，但它也总是会
it's always going to be better to hook
钩总是更好
into some kind of automated pipeline as
进入某种自动化管道
you go further further downstream down
你向下游走得更远
the tools of production system so a few
生产系统的工具
just a few words of warning always
总是警告几句话
automate it downstream of their always
使它们始终处于下游
make it part of its the I process I
使它成为我处理过程的一部分
would say that the next one's burnt me
会说下一个被我烧死
before stay as close as you can see the
待在你可以看到的附近
production platform don't try and frig
生产平台不要尝试
around with integration tests and
与集成测试和
everything that that you think like the
您认为的所有内容
production system and not it's not worth
生产系统，不是不值得
it because you know especially with that
因为你特别知道
battery for instance it's so cheap to
例如电池便宜
create a new environment why would you
创建一个新的环境，为什么你会
do anything else and you know
做其他事情，你知道
fundamentally don't redeploy everything
根本不重新部署所有内容
for every change because you'll get to
进行每一次更改，因为您将
the point where it's just not possible I
我不可能的那一点
think we're going to have to yeah okay
认为我们将不得不不得不
so how would you do bug a request I was
所以你会如何处理我的请求
going to do a couple of the demos with
将与做一些演示
the trace endpoint I can show the trace
跟踪端点，我可以显示跟踪
endpoint I've got ya might as well just
我有的端点可能也一样
show that quickly there you go so these
表明你很快就去了，所以这些
are that's not a very good one but
那不是很好吗，但是
here's my last request 22 / and it gives
这是我的最后一个请求22 /
requests headers response headers
请求头响应头
statuses etc yeah I find that quite
状态等等，是的，我发现
useful with them with the Zulu proxy as
与Zulu代理一起对他们有用
well so if you're doing
好吧，如果你在做
api gateway patent you can see the the
api网关专利，您可以看到
first request and then you can see the
首先请求，然后您可以看到
proxy to request as well which is very
代理请求以及这是非常
strong okay finally finally finally a
坚强还可以，终于终于有了
next one how do you get the middle we're
下一个你如何获得我们中间
ready if you're going to test something
准备好要测试什么
locally it's a pain so I have to you
在当地很痛苦，所以我不得不
know reset the state every time you want
知道每次都想重置状态
to run it a suite of tests so that the
进行一系列测试，以便
thing i always use these days is dhaka
这些天我经常使用的东西是dhaka
dr. de Campos is absolutely perfect yeah
博士de Campos绝对完美
because you can just blow away to stay
因为你可以吹走留下
and start from from from scratch okay
然后从头开始好
fine okay so how do you discover and do
很好，那你怎么发现和做
di on middleware so the that's another
di在中间件上，那是另一个
thing about 12 factor right make it the
关于12要素的事情使之成为
same everywhere you go and one way to do
无论您走到哪里都一样，一种方法
that if you spring cloud connectors a
如果您弹起云连接器
bit i'm actually not a big fan of using
有点我实际上不是使用的忠实粉丝
them for everything but i can talk about
他们的一切，但我可​​以谈论
the detail more more if anybody's
如果有人的话，更多细节
interested and then I think that is
感兴趣，然后我认为那是
finally the end isn't it the last side
最终结局不是最后一面
is about yeah okay different ways of
是的，好吧，不同的方式
provisioning so everybody's got a
供应，所以每个人都有
favorite dr. compose i think is great
最喜欢的博士我认为很棒
for middleware it's great because you
对于中间件来说很棒，因为您
can just blow everything away all other
可以吹走其他所有东西
people use at these other things
人们在其他地方使用
VirtualBox each one yeah yeah my
VirtualBox每个人，是的，是的，我的
colleagues here still have my milds
这里的同事还有我的温柔
VirtualBox configuration running so with
VirtualBox配置如此运行
them with Agron you can do vary based
他们与阿格隆，你可以做基于
VirtualBox locally and kind of lots of
VirtualBox在本地，很多
different remote systems now as well
现在也可以使用不同的远程系统
counting so vagrants are really nice too
计数，所以流浪者也很好
much compose actually can start to do
实际上可以开始做很多工作
that yeah yeah AWS now as these
是的，现在是AWS，因为这些
documents doesn't it okay so different
文件不好，如此不同
there's different approaches to that and
有不同的方法，
then finally just think just just got
然后最后只是觉得刚刚得到
some links at the end because we do have
最后一些链接，因为我们确实有
to finish so if anybody wants to follow
完成，所以如果有人想跟随
up on this come and ask is I'm going to
来问问我要去
disappear because I've really going to
消失，因为我真的要
present get ready for another
现在为另一个做准备
presentation Spencer will be here we're
演示文稿斯宾塞将在这里我们
all here the whole week so come in come
整个星期都在这里，所以进来吧
in stoppers and talk about any of these
在塞子上谈论这些
things a lot of it you can tell his work
事情很多，你可以告诉他的工作
in progress we're thinking about it hard
在进行中，我们正在努力思考
we're developing hard and we're going to
我们正在努力发展，我们将
start pushing the tools in this
开始推动工具
direction starting from now basically so
从现在开始的方向基本上是这样
if you have opinions if you've you know
如果您有意见，如果您知道
got some battle stories and definitely
有一些战斗故事，而且肯定
we definitely like to hear
我们绝对喜欢听到
as well so thanks very much just thank
也非常感谢
everyone you have to see you soon
每个人都必须很快见到你
you
您